petronas.com 2017-05-13

# Privacy Policy | PETRONAS

  1. Home > **Privacy Policy** 

#### Information sharing 

PETRONAS only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of the organisation in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of PETRONAS, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If PETRONAS and/or its subsidiaries, affiliated companies and other trusted businesses or persons become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide prior notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

####   
Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorised access to or unauthorised alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorised access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to PETRONAS’ employees, contractors and third parties who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These entities are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

####   
Enforcement

PETRONAS regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between PETRONAS and an individual or organisation.

####   
Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice on a best-case basis (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).​ 

​
